Cook, Alice Papers /3012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Series VI: Subject Files
  - Sub-Series A. U.S. Files
    - Hawaii-Nurses (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Hawaii-Pay equity (Box 30, Folder 25-28)
    - Hawaii-Project info (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Hawaii-Sexual Harassment (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Hawaii-Traditional and national values (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Hawaii-UHPA (University of Hawaii Professional Assembly) (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Hawaii-Women (Box 30, Folder 33-34)
    - Health and safety (Box 31, Folder 1-5)
    - Health and safety-General (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Health and safety-Hospitals (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Health and safety, 1976-1984 (Box 31, Folder 8-12)
    - Health and safety, 1985-1996 (Box 31, Folder 13-16)
    - Health and safety-Plans (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Health and safety-Pregnancy (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Health and safety-Urbanization (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Health and safety-Video display terminals (Box 31, Folder 20-21)
    - Health Care Careers (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Health Care Insurance (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Higher Education-Discrimination (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - History (Box 31, Folder 25-26)
    - History-Biography (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - History, 1970-1984 (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
    - History, 1975-1974 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - History, 1985-1990 (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
    - History, 1990-1996 (Box 32, Folder 7-9)
    - Hours (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Hours of Work-Flex Time (Box 32, Folder 11-12)
    - Hours of Work-Part Time (Box 32, Folder 13-16)
    - Household (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Immigration (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - International Women's Year (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Job Satisfaction (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Job Segregation (Box 32, Folder 21-24)
    - Job Sharing (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Labor-Critique (Box 32, Folder 26-27)
    - Labor Management Conferences (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - U.S. Labor Market Policy (Box 33, Folder 1-5)
    - LMPO II (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Labor Market Policy (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
    - Labor Market Policy, 1975-1989 (Box 33, Folder 9-10)
    - LMPr (Labor Market Practice) (Box 33, Folder 11-19)
    - LMPr-Absenteeism (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - LMPr-Academic (Box 33, Folder 21-24)
    - LMPr-Careers (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - LMPr-Coal Employment (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - LMPr-CETA (Comprehensive Employment & Training Act) (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - LMPr-Contingent Workers (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - LMPr-Cooperation (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - LMPr-Cornell University (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - LMPr-Disabled (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - LMPr-Discrimination (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - LMPr-Economy (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - LMPr-Employment (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - LMPr-Future (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - LMPr-Glass ceiling (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - LMPr-Home (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - LMPr-Job segregation (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - LMPr-Military (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - LMPr-Mobility (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - LMPr, 1980-1985 (Box 34, Folder 17-20)
    - LMPr, 1986-1990 (Box 34, Folder 21-22)
    - LMPr III, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - LMPr-Non-traditional (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - LMPr-Non-traditional jobs (Box 34, Folder 25-27)
    - LMPr-Nurses (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - LMPr-Occupational Choice-Division of Labor (Box 34, Folder 29-30)
    - LMPr-Promotion (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - LMPr-Reentry (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - LMPr-Remedy (Box 34, Folder 33-34)
    - LMPR-Restructuring (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - LMPr-Retirement (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - LMPr-Satisfaction (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - LMPr-Sexual Harassment (Box 34, Folder 38-39)
    - LMPr-Small Business (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - LMPr-Sweatshops (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - LMPr-Unemployment (Box 34, Folder 42-43)
    - LMPr-White Collar (Box 34, Folder 45-47)
    - Labor market practice-wingspread (Box 34, Folder 48-51)
    - LMPr-Workplace Violence (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Labor movement (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
    - Labor participation-community (Box 35, Folder 3-4)
    - Labor Union-Local (Box 35, Folder 5-6)
    - Laws (Box 35, Folder 7-16)
    - Laws-Women (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Leadership (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Low Income (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Married Women (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Maternity and Child Care Leave (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Maternity Leave (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Media Report to Women (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Men (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Migrant labor (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Minorities (Box 35, Folder 26-30)
    - Minorities-African American (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Minorities-Hispanic (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - National Labor Relations Board (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - New York State (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - New York State-Women (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Newspaper Negotiations (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Nurses (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Occupational Choice (Box 35, Folder 38-39)
    - Other Workers (Box 35, Folder 40-43)
    - Other Services (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - U.S. Pensions (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Perkins, Frances (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Pioneer Women (Box 36, Folder 3-4)
    - Political Action (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Politics (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
    - Policy (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Poverty (Box 36, Folder 9-14)
    - Pregnancy (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Printing (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Professional Women (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Protective Legislation (Box 36, Folder 18-19)
    - Racism (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Railroad Labor Act (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Reentry (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Remedy (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Research and Report (Box 36, Folder 24-25)
    - Research and Resources (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Right to Work (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Rural Women (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Salary Banding (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - School Law (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Sexual Abuse (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Sexual Harassment (Box 36, Folder 32-35)
    - Sexuality (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Social Policy (Box 36, Folder 37-38)
    - Steel (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Student Demonstrations (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Supervision (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Taft-Hartley (Bills Preceding) (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
    - Taxation and Social Security Law (Box 37, Folder 3-7)
    - U.S. Taxes-Social Security (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Technology (Box 37, Folder 9-10)
    - Teens (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Textile Workers (19th century) (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Theory (Box 37, Folder 13-15)
    - Theory of Government (Box 37, Folder 16-19)
    - Title IX (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Trade Unions-Activity (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Trade Unions-Affirmative Action (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Trade Unions -Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Trade Unions -American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE) (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Trade Unions-AFL-CIO (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Trade Unions-Department for Professional Employees (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Trade Unions-AFSCME (Box 37, Folder 27-29)
    - Trade Unions-Association for Union Democracy (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Trade Unions-Association of Flight Attendants (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Trade Unions-Coalition of Labor Union Women (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Trade Unions-College Bargaining (Box 37, Folder 33-36)
    - Trade Unions-Comunications Workers (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Trade Unions-Cornell Organization for Labor Action (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Trade Unions-Doctor's Union (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Trade Unions-Education (Box 37, Folder 40-41)
    - Trade Unions-Family (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Trade Unions-Flight Attendants (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Trade Unions-Flint Glass (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Trade Unions-General (Box 37, Folder 45-50)
    - Trade Unions-General (Box 38, Folder 1-10)
    - Trade Unions-Graphic Arts (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Trade Unions-Health and Hospital (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Trade Unions-Health and Safety (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Trade Unions-History (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Trade Unions-Hotel and Restaurant Employees (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Trade Unions-Housing (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Trade Unions-Independence (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Trade Unions-International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Trade Unions-International Ladies Garment Workers (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Trade Unions-International Union of Electricians (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Trade Unions-Interviews (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Trade Unions-Job Training (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Trade Unions-Labor Education (Box 38, Folder 23-27)
    - Trade Unions-Labor Market Policy (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Trade Unions-Leadership (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Trade Unions-Local 1199 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Trade Unions-Meat Cutters Union (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Trade Unions-Mergers (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Trade Unions-Networking (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Trade Unions-Nine to Five (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Trade Unions-Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAW) (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Trade Unions-Organization (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Trade Unions-Organizing (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Trade Unions-Policy and Practice (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Trade Unions-Politics (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Trade Unions-Professional Employees (Box 38, Folder 40-41)
    - Trade Unions-Public Employees (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Trade Unions-Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU) (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Trade Unions-Service Employees International Union (SEIU) (Box 38, Folder 44-45)
    - Trade Unions-Social Workers (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - Trade Unions-Structure (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - Trade Unions-Teamsters (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - Trade Unions-Textile Workers (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - Trade Unions-Workfare (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - Trade Unions-Theory (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - Trade Unions-United Auto Workers (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - Trade Unions-United Mine Workers (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - Trade Unions-United Steel Workers (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - Trade Unions-Vocational Training (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - Trade Unions-Wages (Box 38, Folder 56)
    - Trade Unions-Women (Box 39, Folder 1-3)
    - Trade Unions-Women-Interview (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Trade Unions-Women-Proposal (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
    - Traditional Values (Box 39, Folder 7-16)
    - Transit Bill (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Unemployment (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Union and Community (Box 39, Folder 19-22)
    - Union Democracy (Box 39, Folder 23-24)
    - From Notebook Readings on Union Democracy (Box 39, Folder 25-26)
    - Union Education (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Union Government (Box 39, Folder 28-30)
    - Unions-Ronnie S. Ratner Project Papers (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
    - United Auto Workers (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - US Department of Labor (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Urbanization (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Violence (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Vocational Education (Box 40, Folder 8-10)
    - Voluntary Associations (Box 40, Folder 11-13)
    - Wage Gap (Box 40, Folder 14-15)
    - Wages (Box 40, Folder 16-17)
    - Wages, Minimum (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Welfare (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Welfare, 1989-1994 (Box 40, Folder 20-21)
    - Welfare to Work (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - White Collar (Box 40, Folder 23-25)
    - Women and Politics (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Women-Eleanor Marx (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Women-Employment discrimination (Box 40, Folder 28-30)
    - Women-General (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Women-Harassment (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Women in Unions (Box 40, Folder 33-35)
    - Women-Legislation (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Women Workers-19th century (Box 40, Folder 37-38)
    - Women-Reentry (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Women-Trade Unions (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Women-WWII (Box 40, Folder 41-42)
    - Women's Agenda (Box 40, Folder 43-44)
    - Women's Issues (union clauses) (Box 40, Folder 45-46)
    - Women's Movement (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Women's Organization (Box 41, Folder 2-3)
    - Women's organizations-Cornell University (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Women's Studies (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Women's Way (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Work Culture (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Worker's Education (Box 41, Folder 8-13)
    - Worker's Education-ALES (American Labor Education Service) (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Working Women (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Working Women-Ithaca (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series B. Japan
    - Sub-Series 1. Subject Files
      - Anti-war youth (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
      - Asian labor (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Asian Women Workers Center (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Automation (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Bibliography (Box 42, Folder 6-7)
      - Censorship (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Child Care-Demography (Box 42, Folder 9-12)
      - Coal Industry (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Collective Bargaining (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - "Comfort Women" (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - Conference on Modern Japan (Box 42, Folder 16-18)
      - Culture (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Day Care (Box 42, Folder 20-21)
      - Demography (Box 42, Folder 22-24)
      - Discrimination (Box 42, Folder 25-29)
      - Economicy Policy (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
      - Economics (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Economy (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Education (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Employers Organization (Box 43, Folder 6-7)
      - Employment (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Equal Opportunity (Box 43, Folder 9-10)
      - Equal Pay (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Equality (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Family (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - General (Box 43, Folder 14-26)
      - General (Box 44, Folder 1-24)
      - General (Box 45, Folder 1-17)
      - Health and Safety (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - History (Box 45, Folder 19-21)
      - Hours (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - Industrial Relations (Box 45, Folder 23)
      - Industry (Box 45, Folder 24-26)
      - Institute of Labor (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
      - Insurance (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - International Committee of Free Trade (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - IHJ Bulletin (International House of Japan) (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - International Labor Organization (ILO) (Box 46, Folder 7-11)
      - ILO Deliberation Council (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - ILO-Dreyer Report (Box 46, Folder 13-15)
      - Jichiro (Box 46, Folder 16-21)
      - Labor (Box 46, Folder 22)
      - Labor Administration (Box 46, Folder 23)
      - Labor and Politics (Box 46, Folder 24)
      - Labor Banks (Box 46, Folder 25)
      - Labor Education (Box 46, Folder 26)
      - Labor-General (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - Labor Law (Box 46, Folder 28-30)
      - Labor Leaders (Box 46, Folder 31)
      - Labor Legislation (Box 46, Folder 32-32a)
      - Labor Market (Box 46, Folder 33)
      - Labor Market Policy (Box 46, Folder 34-36)
      - Labor Market Practice (Box 47, Folder 1-13)
      - Labor Migration (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - Labor Ministry (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Labor Movement (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - Labor Relations (Box 47, Folder 17-19)
      - Labor Statistics (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - Law (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - Local Government (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - Management (Box 47, Folder 23-24)
      - Maternity Leave (Box 47, Folder 25)
      - Medium and Small Enterprises (Box 47, Folder 26)
      - Minorities (Box 47, Folder 27)
      - National Govnerment-NPA (National Personnel Authority) (Box 47, Folder 28)
      - Naven (Box 47, Folder 29)
      - Nevins, Thomas (Box 47, Folder 30)
      - New Left (Box 47, Folder 31)
      - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Older Workers (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Peace Organizations (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Pensions (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Personnel Administration (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Political Action (Box 48, Folder 6-8)
      - Political Action-Communist Party (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Political Action-Democratic Socialist Party (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Political Action-Liberal Democratic Party (Box 48, Folder 11-12)
      - Political Parties (Box 48, Folder 13-15)
      - Politics-Democratic Socialist Party (Box 48, Folder 16-17)
      - Political Parties-Liberal Democratic (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Political Parties-Socialist (Box 48, Folder 19-24)
      - Politics (Box 48, Folder 25-27)
      - Politics and Labor (Box 48, Folder 28-29)
      - Politics-Communist Party (Box 48, Folder 30-31)
      - Politics-General (Box 48, Folder 32)
      - Polls (Box 48, Folder 33)
      - Posts (Box 48, Folder 34)
      - Private Union Council (Box 48, Folder 35)
      - Protective Legislation (Box 48, Folder 36-37)
      - Public Unions (Box 48, Folder 38)
      - Public Workers (Box 48, Folder 39)
      - Remedies (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Research (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Salaries (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Sexual Harassment (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Statistics (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Students (Box 49, Folder 6-7)
      - Taxation and Social Security Law (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Teachers (Box 49, Folder 9-11)
      - Technical Cooperation (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Technology (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Textiles (Box 49, Folder 14-15)
      - Trade Unions (Box 49, Folder 16-27)
      - Trade Unions-Constitutions (Box 49, Folder 28)
      - Trade Unions-Denki Roren (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Trade Unions-Domei (Box 50, Folder 2-3)
      - Trade Unions-International Metalworkers Federation (IMF) (Box 50, Folder 4-5)
      - Trade Unions-Membership Statistics (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Trade Unions-Policy and Practice (Box 50, Folder 7-11)
      - Trade Unions-Public Employees (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Trade Unions-Railway (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - Trade Unions-Shitetsu Soren (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Trade Unions-Sohyo (Box 50, Folder 15-21)
      - Trade Unions-Spring Struggle (Box 50, Folder 22)
      - Trade Unions-Steel Industry (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - Trade Unions-Strike (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - Trade Unions-Structure (Box 50, Folder 25)
      - Trade Unions-Zentei (Box 50, Folder 26-27)
      - Traditional Values (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - Traditional Women's Roles (Box 50, Folder 29)
      - Unemployment (Box 50, Folder 30)
      - Unemployment insurance (Box 50, Folder 31)
      - Unification (Box 50, Folder 32-33)
      - Wages (Box 50, Folder 34-42)
      - Women (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Women's Organization (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Workers (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Workers-Sociological Studies (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Workers-Temporary (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Workers-Women (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Workers-Youth (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Youth-Union and Politics (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Sub-Series 2. Project files
      - Administration (Box 51, Folder 9-14)
      - Administration - Fulbright (Box 51, Folder 15-17)
      - Lecture (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - Administration-Reports (Box 51, Folder 19)
      - Administration-Sabbatic (Box 51, Folder 20-21)
      - Trip Report (Box 51, Folder 22)
      - Visitors (Box 51, Folder 23)
      - Interviews (Box 51, Folder 24-37)
      - Manuscripts, Drafts, Notes (Box 51, Folder 38-41)
      - Mss/drafts/notes (con't) (Box 52, Folder 1-21)
      - Diaries (Box 52, Folder 22-27)
      - Journals (Box 52, Folder 28-30)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 1-4)
      - Public workerrs scrapbook, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous files (Box 53, Folder 6-8)
  - Sub-Series C. Other Countries
    - Africa (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
    - Albania (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Antigua (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Arab Countries (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Argentina (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Asia (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Australia-Affirmative Action (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Australia-Bibliography (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Australia-Child Care (Box 54, Folder 10-19)
    - Australia-Demographics (Box 54, Folder 20-22)
    - Australia-Demography (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Australia-Discrimination (Box 54, Folder 24-28)
    - Australia-Education (Box 54, Folder 29-31)
    - Australia-Education of Women (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
    - Australia-Education-Vocational Training (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Australia-Equal Opportunity (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Australia-Equal Pay (Box 55, Folder 5-7)
    - Australia-Equality (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Australia-Family (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Australia-Foreign Workers (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Australia-General (Box 55, Folder 11-12)
    - Health and Safety (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Australia-Hours of work (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Australia-Labor Market Policy (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Australia-Labor Market Practice (Box 55, Folder 16-22)
    - Australia-Laws and Legislation (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Australia-Maternity Leave (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Australia-Other Services (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Australia-Political Parties (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Australia-Protective Legislation (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Australia-Reports (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Australia-Social Services (Box 55, Folder 29-33)
    - Australia-Taxation and Social Security Law (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - Australia-Technology (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Australia-Trade Union Policy and Practice (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
    - Australia-Trade Unions (Box 56, Folder 3-5)
    - Australia-Traditional and National Values (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Australia-Traditional Values (Box 56, Folder 7-8)
    - Australia-Western Australia Employees Federation (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Australia-Wages (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Australia-Women and Work (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Australia-Women's Organizations (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Australia-Women's Trade Union Commission (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Austria-Bibliography (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Austria-Child Care (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Austria-Demographic Data (Box 56, Folder 16-17)
    - Austria-Demography (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Austria-Discrimination (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Austria-EU (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Austria-Education of Women (Box 56, Folder 21-22)
    - Austria-Equality (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Austria-Family (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Austria-General (Box 56, Folder 25-36)
    - Austria-History (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Austria-Hours (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Austria-Household Bills (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Austria-Law (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Austria-Labor Market Policy (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Austria-Labor Market Practice (Box 57, Folder 6-8)
    - Austria-Law and Equal Opportunity (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Austria-Maternity Leave (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Austria-Political Parties (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Austria-Technology (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Austria-Trade Union Policy and Practice (Box 57, Folder 13-16)
    - Austria-Trade Unions (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Austria-Traditional nd National Values (Box 57, Folder 18-19)
    - Austria-Wages (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Belgium (Box 57, Folder 21-27)
    - Brazil (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Bulgaria (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - Canada-Abortion (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Canada-Bibliography (Box 58, Folder 2-6)
    - Canada-Child Care (Box 58, Folder 7-8)
    - Canada-Comparable Worth, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 9-11)
    - Canada-Day Care (Box 58, Folder 12-15)
    - Canada-Demography (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Canada-Demographic Data (Box 58, Folder 17-18)
    - Canada-Discrimination (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Canada-Equal Opportunity (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Canada-Equal Pay (Box 58, Folder 21-22)
    - Canada-Equal Pay, 1981-1989 (Box 58, Folder 23-25)
    - Canada-Equality (Box 58, Folder 26-27)
    - Canada-Equality (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - Canada-Equality, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Canada-Family (Box 59, Folder 4-7)
    - Canada-Family Poverty (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Canada-Foreign Workers (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Canada-General (Box 59, Folder 10-15)
    - Canada-Health and Safety (Box 59, Folder 16-17)
    - Canada-History (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Canada-Hours Part Time (Box 59, Folder 19-20)
    - Canada-Job Evaluation (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Canada-Labor Market Practice (LMPr) (Box 59, Folder 22-23)
    - Canada-Labor Market Practice, Trade Unions (Box 59, Folder 24-26)